TV's most f'ed up series... is about to eff up the movies.
The Drawn Together Movie: The Movie! is a animation,
comedy, mystery film directed by Greg Franklin.
When the mystery-solving musician Foxxy Love notices she and her fellow housemates can curse without being
bleeped—something they've never been able to do before—she realizes their show has been canceled.
Determined to get back on the air, the gang travels to
Make-A-Point-Land in order to get a point (and get back on the air).
Spanky Ham (voice), played by Adam Carolla.
Ling-Ling (voice), played by Abbey DiGregorio.
Captain Hero / King / Wile E. Coyote (voice), played by Jess Harnell.
I.S.R.A.E.L. (aka Intelligent Smart Robotic Animated Eraser
Lady) (voice), played by Seth MacFarlane.
Xandir P. Whifflebottom (voice), played by Jack Plotnick.
Toot Braunstein / Princess Clara (voice), played by Tara Strong.
The Drawn Together Movie: The Movie!
(also known as The Drawn Together Movie or Drawn Together: The Movie) is a
2010 American adult animated parody musical black comedy film.
It is based on the Comedy Central animated sitcom Drawn Together, written and executive produced by creators
Dave Jeser and Matt Silverstein, produced by Richard Quan, and directed by Greg Franklin.
The film is the first Drawn Together release since the TV show's
cancellation, and the film itself deals with the subject.
It is the second animated film from Comedy Central,
after South Park: Bigger, Longer & Uncut.
The original cast returned to voice their characters and features the guest voice of Seth MacFarlane as
"I.S.R.A.E.L." (Intelligent Smart Robot Animation Eraser Lady), and Vernon Wells as the villainous Network Head.
While the television series was produced and animated by Rough Draft Studios using digital ink and paint, the film was instead produced and
animated by 6 Point Harness and done entirely in flash animation using Toon Boom and Adobe Flash Professional due to budget cuts.
The film received a generally negative reception.
The film explores themes of parody, adult animation, fictional reality tv.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.